constructiondeal.com 2009-07-04

# ConstructionDeal.com - Privacy Policy

## For Our Project Owners:

Personal information and other data collected

  * ConstructionDeal.com collects personal information when property owners register for our service and voluntarily provide such information.
  * The personal information will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.

The Type of Information We Need from our Project Owners

  * Name
  * Phone Number
  * Email Address

How the Information is Utilized to Help You Complete Your Project

  * We use the information you provide about yourself and your project, when registering with us, only to complete our service. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that process.
  * We email you the information on each and every service provider who previewed your project details and requested your contact information.
  * We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.
  * Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

For information about specific ConstructionDeal.com services or additional questions about our privacy policy, please contact our Customer Service Department at [support@constructiondeal.com](mailto:support@constructiondeal.com) or call at 866-663-4711.  
Or write to us at:

ConstructionDeal.com  
5152 Sepulveda Blvd. Suite 114  
Sherman Oaks, CA 91403 

This Policy applies to all of the services and websites offered by ConstructionDeal.com or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies.

## For Our Service Providers:

Professional Information and Other Data Collected

  * ConstructionDeal.com collects professional information when service providers register or subscribe to our service and voluntarily provide such information.
  * Your professional information will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.

The Type of Information We Collect from our Service Providers

  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone Number
  * Email Address
  * Credit Card Information

How the Information is Utilized to Help You Find Prospects

  * We use the information you provide about yourself and your company, when registering or subscribing with us, only to complete our service. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that process.
  * We will only provide your business contact information to project owners who's contact information you requested to view and not to any outside parties.
  * We use your email address for communication purpose. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
  * We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.
  * Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Security

  * We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
  * We ask that you report to us immediately if you feel your contact information has been used inappropriately
